export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is an example of an Operating System(OS)?",
    answers: ["Microsoft Office", "Adobe Photoshop", "Windows 10", "Wikipedia"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a portable computer?",
    answers: ["Desktop", "Laptop", "Booknote", "CompuLight"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What memory capacity listed below is the largest?",
    answers: ["100,000 MB", "1,000,000 KB", "1,000 GB", "10,000 TB"],
    correct: 3,
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a web browser?",
    answers: ["Chrome", "Firefox", "Opera", "Maxtron"],
    correct: 3,
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What device is used to display information from a computer?",
    answers: ["Mouse", "Speakers", "Monitor", "USB"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "What WWW stands for?",
    answers: [
      "World Web Wired",
      "Websites World Wonders",
      "Word World Webs",
      "World Wide Web",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "What is an ISP?",
    answers: [
      "International Special Police",
      "Internet Service Provider",
      "Internal Security Protocol",
      "Internet Service Program",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a storage device?",
    answers: [
      "Solid-State Drive",
      "Motherboard",
      "Network Adapter",
      "Graphics Card",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question: "What is a folder?",
    answers: [
      "A virus",
      "A bug",
      "A container of files",
      "A location on a website",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "The hexadecimal number system consists of what symbols?",
    answers: ["0 – 7", "0 – 9 , A – F", "0 – 7, A – F", "0 - 1"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Compact discs, (according to the original CD specifications) hold how many minutes of music?",
    answers: ["74 min", "90 min", "56 min", "60 min"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is an example of non-volatile memory?",
    answers: ["Cache memory", "RAM", "ROM", "IOPS"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the definition of shareware?",
    answers: [
      "Free Software",
      "Free Software on a trial basis",
      "Software never launched",
      "Shared data on a computer",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of malware blocks access to data unless the victim pays money?",
    answers: ["Adware", "Ransomware", "Trojan Horse", "Spyware"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the error message of HTTP 404?",
    answers: ["Not found", "Forbidden", "OK", "Bad request"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 15,
  },
];
